Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Interviews
  - The National Society Daughters of the American Revolution QSOS
    - Jacqueline Collopy oral history interview conducted by Melissa Danielsson, 2009-04-27 (Interview-id GA30075-DAR003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 5 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 5 digital images; afc2007009_GA30075_DAR003_06.doc; afc2007009_GA30075_DAR003_01-05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR716
    - Violette Denney oral history interview conducted by Kimber Pepper, 2008-10-22 (Interview-id GA30116-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images), 2 4x6 color prints; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_GA30116_DAR001_01.doc; afc2007009_GA30116_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_GA30116_DAR001_03.jpg; afc2007009_GA30116_DAR001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_GA30116_DAR001_05.mp3
    - Brenda Fenimore oral history interview conducted by Nancy Currier, 2007-01-21 (Interview-id GA30215-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 2 4"x6" color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR535
    - Martha Davis oral history interview conducted by Bill Ledford, 2008-01-14 (Interview-id GA30474-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 color prints - one 2.75" x 3.125", one 8.5" x 11", 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_GA30474_DAR001_03.doc; afc2007009_GA30474_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_GA30474_DAR001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR562
    - Barbara Bone oral history interview conducted by Ann Atkinson, 2008-01-14 (Interview-id GA30582-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 color printout (from digital image), 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_GA30582_001_01.doc; afc2007009_GA30582_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR563
    - Emily Temple oral history interview conducted by Joann Kensler Gordon, 2010-02-25 (Interview-id GA30643-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR001_03.doc; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR826
    - Joann Kensler Gordon oral history interview conducted by Emily Temple, 2010-02-25 (Interview-id GA30643-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR002_03.doc; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR002_01.jpg; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR002_02.jpg; afc2007009_GA30643_DAR002_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR789
    - Diane Hom oral history interview, 2006-03-11 (Interview-id HI98617-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 5 b/w printouts (from digital images)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR325
    - Maurine King oral history interview conducted by Diane Hom, 2005-01-23 (Interview-id HI98617-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR324
    - Caitilin Embree oral history interview conducted by Kathryn Koos-Lee, 2008-11-07 (Interview-id HI98617-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 5 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 5 digital images; afc2007009_HI98617_DAR002_06.doc; afc2007009_HI98617_DAR002_01-05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR640
    - Kellie Wachter oral history interview conducted by Kathryn Koos-Lee, 2009-04-29 (Interview-id HI98617-DAR003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_HI98617_DAR003_03.doc; afc2007009_HI98617_DAR003_01.jpg; afc2007009_HI98617_DAR003_02.jpg; afc2007009_HI98617_DAR003_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR717
    - Janet Lehman oral history interview conducted by Dorothy Crooks, 2008-08-13 (Interview-id IA50036-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IA50036_002_01.rtf; afc2007009_IA50036_002_02.jpg; afc2007009_IA50036_002_03.jpg; afc2007009_IA50036_002_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR642
    - Dorothea Stratton oral history interview conducted by Dorothy Crooks, 2008-01-30 (Interview-id IA50036-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Letter to Stratton, 2 copies of transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 9 digital images; afc2007009_IA50036_DAR001_10.rtf; afc2007009_IA50036_DAR001_01-09.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR564
    - Raola Giles oral history interview conducted by Debbie Strickland, 2008-01-30 (Interview-id IA50201-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IA50201_DAR001_04.doc; afc2007009_IA50201_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_IA50201_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_IA50201_DAR001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR565
    - Janice Juchems oral history interview conducted by Dorothy Crooks, 2009-09-30 (Interview-id IA50621-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IA50621_DAR001_04.doc; afc2007009_IA50621_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_IA50621_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_IA50621_DAR001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR718
    - Deenie Schuchert oral history interview conducted by Colleen Lemkuil, 2009-10-06 (Interview-id IA51360-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_IA51360_DAR001_03.doc; afc2007009_IA51360_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_IA51360_DAR001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR719
    - Anita "Billie" Rosendahl oral history interview conducted by Colleen Lemkuil, 2009-10-12 (Interview-id IA51360-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IA51360_DAR002_04.doc; afc2007009_IA51360_DAR002_01.jpg; afc2007009_IA51360_DAR002_02.jpg; afc2007009_IA51360_DAR002_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR720
    - Onalee Arnold oral history interview conducted by Patricia Otis, 2009-02-06 (Interview-id IA52302-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_IA52302_DAR001_05.doc; afc2007009_IA52302_DAR001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR641
    - Judith Robinette oral history interview conducted by Carol Klopfenstein, 2009-01-12 (Interview-id IA52659-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IA52659_001_04.doc; afc2007009_IA52659_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_IA52659_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_IA52659_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR643
    - Verna Quinlin oral history interview conducted by Carol Klopfenstein, 2009-03-10 (Interview-id IA52659-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IA52659_002_01.doc; afc2007009_IA52659_002_02.jpg; afc2007009_IA52659_002_03.jpg; afc2007009_IA52659_002_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR644
    - Marilyn Lambert oral history interview conducted by Carol Klopfenstein, 2009-03-23 (Interview-id IA52659-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_IA52659_003_04.doc; afc2007009_IA52659_003_01.jpg; afc2007009_IA52659_003_02.jpg; afc2007009_IA52659_003_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR645
    - Cecilia Giberson oral history interview conducted by Diane Greene, 2006-10-14 (Interview-id ID83301-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR339
    - Mary Stewart oral history interview conducted by Karen Stewart, 2008-12-27 (Interview-id IL61614-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_IL61614_DAR001_05.doc; afc2007009_IL61614_DAR001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR647
    - Jan Eyman oral history interview conducted by Norma L. Belt, 2007-03-09 (Interview-id IL62246-004)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_IL62246_004_03.doc; afc2007009_IL62246_004_01.jpg; afc2007009_IL62246_004_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR605
    - Betty Boehm oral history interview conducted by Norma L. Belt, 2007-03-22 (Interview-id IL62246-005)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_IL62246_005_03.doc; afc2007009_IL62246_005_01.jpg; afc2007009_IL62246_005_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR651
    - Betty Eyman oral history interview conducted by Norma L. Belt, 2007-03-14 (Interview-id IL62246-006)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_IL62246_006_03.doc; afc2007009_IL62246_006_01.jpg; afc2007009_IL62246_006_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR652
    - Norma L. Belt oral history interview conducted by Karen G. Bauer, 2007-02-09 (Interview-id IL62246DAR-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_IL62246DAR_001_01.doc; afc2007009_IL62246DAR_001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR648
    - Brenda Thiems oral history interview conducted by Norma L. Belt, 2007-03-09 (Interview-id IL62246-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout (from digital image); 1 digital document, 1 digital image; afc2007009_IL62246_DAR002_01.doc; afc2007009_IL62246_DAR002_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR596
    - Anna Hecox oral history interview conducted by Ruth Cole, 2010-02-24 (Interview-id IL62301-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_IL62301_DAR001_05.doc; afc2007009_IL62301_DAR001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR785
    - Marian Brockschmidt oral history interview conducted by Betty Wilson, 2008-01-23 (Interview-id IL62530-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 4"x6" color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR567
    - Carol Elmore oral history interview conducted by Susan Metzger, 2009-07-23 (Interview-id KS66502-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KS66502_DAR001_01.rtf; afc2007009_KS66502_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_KS66502_DAR001_03.jpg; afc2007009_KS66502_DAR001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR721
    - Pam Neil oral history interview conducted by Kathy Hall, 2009-06-15 (Interview-id KY40223-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY40223_001_01.docx; afc2007009_KY40223_001_03.jpg; afc2007009_KY40223_001_04.jpg; afc2007009_KY40223_001_05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY40223_001_02.wav
    - Joann Threet oral history interview conducted by Kathy Hall, 2009-11-05 (Interview-id KY40359-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_KY40359_DAR001_05.doc; afc2007009_KY40359_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_KY40359_DAR001_03.jpg; afc2007009_KY40359_DAR001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_KY40359_DAR001_23.wav
    - Ann Miller oral history interview conducted by Kathy Hall, 2009-03-04 (Interview-id KY40502-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 5 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 5 digital images; afc2007009_KY40502_DAR001_01.docx; afc2007009_KY40502_DAR001_02-06.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR722
    - La Juana Handschin oral history interview conducted by Dorothy Burleigh, 2009-01-21 (Interview-id LA70501-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–3 images; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_LA70501_DAR001_04.doc; afc2007009_LA70501_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_LA70501_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_LA70501_DAR001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR657
    - Lana Laws Downing oral history interview conducted by Margie Laws Luke, 2009-01-23 (Interview-id LA70538-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)–4 images; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_LA70538_DAR001_05.doc; afc2007009_LA70538_DAR001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR658
    - Beverly Cleaver oral history interview conducted by Kathryn Z. Nicodemus, 2009-11-24 (Interview-id MD21793-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MD21793_DAR001_03.jpg; afc2007009_MD21793_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MD21793_DAR001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR758
    - Jeanne Wright oral history interview conducted by Midge Shaw, 2010-03-03 (Interview-id ME04062-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04062_DAR001_01.doc; afc2007009_ME04062_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04062_DAR001_03.jpg; afc2007009_ME04062_DAR001_04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR835
    - Joanne (Jody) Bingham oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-10-28 (Interview-id ME04074-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04074_DAR001_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04074_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04074_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04074_DAR001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR764
    - Ingrid Van Hengel oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-06-23 (Interview-id ME04105-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 6 digital images; afc2007009_ME04105_001_01.doc; afc2007009_ME04105_001_02-07.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR829
    - Kathy Kenny oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2011-10-13 (Interview-id ME04110-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04110_01_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04110_01_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04110_01_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04110_01_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR810
    - Jeanne Bernardy oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2011-11-15 (Interview-id ME04110-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04110_DAR002_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04110_DAR002_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04110_DAR002_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04110_DAR002_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR765
    - Louise Carter oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-08-22 (Interview-id ME04406-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_ME04406_001_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04406_001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR768
    - Wendy Reed oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-04-19 (Interview-id ME04530-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04530_001_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04530_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04530_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04530_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR824
    - Retha Crawford oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-07-23 (Interview-id ME04930-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04930_001_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04930_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04930_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04930_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR762
    - Shirley Farnsworth oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-07-25 (Interview-id ME04930-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04930_002_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04930_002_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04930_002_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04930_002_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR790
    - Kathie Lombard oral history interview conducted by Jeanne Wright, 2010-08-22 (Interview-id ME04971-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_ME04971_001_04.doc; afc2007009_ME04971_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_ME04971_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_ME04971_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR812
    - Marsha Pearson oral history interview conducted by Susan Russ, 2007-09-05 (Interview-id MO63376-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images)–5 images; 1 digital document, 5 digital images; afc2007009_MO63376_DAR001_06.doc; afc2007009_MO63376_DAR001_01-05.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR660
    - Sue Carol Butler Engelman oral history interview conducted by Linda Hardin Sehrt, 2009-11-24 (Interview-id MO64055-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR001_04.doc; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR001_02.jpg; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR778
    - Sharron Lee Gregg oral history interview conducted by Linda Hardin Sehrt, 2009-12-14 (Interview-id MO64055-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR002_04.doc; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR002_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR002_02.jpg; afc2007009_MO64055_DAR002_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR788
    - Suzanne Botts oral history interview conducted by Misty Beatty, 2005-04-01 (Interview-id MO64118-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 1 4x6 color print
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR386
    - Nadine Kennedy oral history interview conducted by Misty Beatty, 2004-11-14 (Interview-id MO64118-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, 1 4x6 color print; 1 digital document; afc2007009_MO64118_DAR002_01.doc
    - Marjorie Doris Frost oral history interview conducted by Linda Hardin Sehrt, 2008-12-05 (Interview-id MO64470-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 4 4x6 color prints; 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MO64470_001_04.doc; afc2007009_MO64470_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO64470_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_MO64470_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR662
    - Louetta Kullmann oral history interview conducted by Judy Frisch, 2007-12-20 (Interview-id MO65338-002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Draft and final transcript, survey, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MO65338_002_03.doc; afc2007009_MO65338_002_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO65338_002_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 2 audiocassettes; AFC 2007/009: SR663; AFC 2007/009: SR664
    - Helen Gregory oral history interview conducted by Judy Frisch, 2007-12-17 (Interview-id MO65338-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images, 1 color printout–6 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_MO65338_DAR001_03.doc; afc2007009_MO65338_DAR001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MO65338_DAR001_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR661
    - Arlene Brown oral history interview conducted by Frieda Hardee, 2008-01-08 (Interview-id MS38701-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Letter to Brown, Brown’s statement, transcript, 6 color prints, 3 b/w printouts (from digital images); 1 digital document, 3 digital images; afc2007009_MS38701_001_04.doc; afc2007009_MS38701_001_01.jpg; afc2007009_MS38701_001_02.jpg; afc2007009_MS38701_001_03.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR570
    - Wendy Ensign Hughes oral history interview conducted by Julee Casey Johnson, 2010-03-03 (Interview-id NC27408-003)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_NC27408_003_05.doc; afc2007009_NC27408_003_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR786
    - Edith Lee Casey oral history interview conducted by Julee Casey Johnson, 2008-10-11 (Interview-id NC27408-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)–3 images, 1 11x14 photocopy of newspaper article; 1 digital document, 4 digital images; afc2007009_NC27408_DAR001_05.docx; afc2007009_NC27408_DAR001_01-04.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR665
    - Johanna Nelson oral history interview conducted by Julee Casey Johnson, 2008-12-14 (Interview-id NC27408-DAR002)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 1 b/w printout–2 images; 1 digital document, 2 digital images; afc2007009_NC27408_DAR002_03.doc; afc2007009_NC27408_DAR002_01.jpg; afc2007009_NC27408_DAR002_02.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR666
    - Betty Ellen Hathaway Madry oral history interview conducted by Frances Price, 2004-02-03 (Interview-id NC27608-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Ethics statement, transcript (20 pages), 2 8x10 color prints
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR387
    - Hilda Clemens oral history interview conducted by Carol Clemens, 2008-10-10 (Interview-id NC27803-001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Transcript, 2 b/w printouts (from digital images)–5 images; 1 digital document, 5 digital images; afc2007009_NC27803_001_02.doc; afc2007009_NC27803_001_03-07.jpg
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_NC27803_001_01.wav
    - Knowles Eveyln oral history interview conducted by Frances Carlton, 2005-01-26 (Interview-id NC27896-DAR001)
      - Manuscripts/Mixed Materials, Interview summary, transcript, 5 4x6 color prints; 1 digital document; afc2007009_NC27896_DAR001_01.doc
      - Sound Recordings, 1 audiocassette; AFC 2007/009: SR388
    - Irene Fankhauser oral history interview conducted by SharonAnn Louden, 2009-12-01 (Interview-id NE68450-DAR001)